Council 82 Security and Law Enforement Employees, AFSCME; Records apap066
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legal Files, 1976-1984; 3; 4.0 cubic ft.
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Stipulations Waiving Certification, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 9)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. Village of Geneseo, Union Brief, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 10)
  - Application of A.J. Scotti, Special Deputy Attorney General, Brief of Appellants--Corrections Officers, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 11)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Attica Correctional Facility (1 of 2) (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 12)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Attica Correctional Facility (2 of 2) (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 13)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits-Attica Correctional Facility, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 14)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Attica Correctional Facility, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 15)
  - Strike of 1979, Hearing Schedules--Attica Correctional Facility, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 16)
  - Strike of 1979, Notices of Determination--Attica Correctional Facility, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 17)
  - Strike of 1979, Note of Determination--Buffalo State, 1979-1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 18)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--SUNY at Buffalo, 1979-1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 19)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Camp Monterey Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 20)
  - Strike of 1979, Common Exhibits-Camp Monterey (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 21)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Camp Monterey, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 22)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Camp Summit (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 23)
  - Strike of 1979, Common Exhibits--Camp Summit (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 24)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Clinton Correctional Facility (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 25)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Clinton Correctional Facility (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 26)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Clinton Correctional Facility (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legal Files), Folder 27)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Downstate Correctional Facllity (1 of 2) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 1)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Downstate Correctional Facllity (2 of 2) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 2)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Downstate Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 3)
  - Strike of 1979, Employee Hearing Schedule--Eastern Correctional Facility (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 4)
  - Strike of 1979, Jack Pellinger--Eastern Correctional Facility, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 5)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Eastern Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 6)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Hearing--Elmira Correctional Facility, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 7)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Great Meadow Correctional Facillty (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 8)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Great Meadow Correctional Facillty (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 9)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination--Great Meadow Correctional Facillty (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 10)
  - Strike of 1979, Strike Correspondence--Great Meadow Correctional Facility, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 11)
  - Strike of 1979, Subpoena Duces Tecum--Middletown Psych. Ctr., 1982 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 12)
  - Strike of 1979, Time and Accrual-Middletown Psych. Ctr., 1980 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 13)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr. (1 of 4) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 14)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr. (2 of 4) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 15)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr. (3 of 4) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 16)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr. (4 of 4) (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 17)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr., 1980 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 18)
  - Strike of 1979, Common Exhlbfts--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr. (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 19)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Hearing--Mid Hudson Psych. Ctr., 1979-1982 (Box 3 (3-Legal Files), Folder 20)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits-Mid Orange Correctional Facility (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 1)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits-Mid Orange Correctional Facility (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 2)
  - Strike of 1979, Common Exhibits--Mid Orange Correctional Facility (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 3)
  - Strike of 1979, Hearing Schedule-Mid Orange Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 4)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination-Mid Orange Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 5)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Hearing-Office of General Services, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 6)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Ossining Correctional Facility (1 of 5), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 7)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Ossining Correctional Facility (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 8)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Ossining Correctional Facility (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 9)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Ossining Correctional Facility (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 10)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavfts--Ossining Correctional Facility (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 11)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Determination-Ossining Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 12)
  - Strike of 1979, Notice of Hearing-Roswell Memorial Park, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 13)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits-Watetown (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 14)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Woodbourne Correctional Facility (1 of 5) (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 15)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Woodbourne Correctional Facility (2 of 5) (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 16)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Woodbourne Correctional Facility (3 of 5) (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 17)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Woodbourne Correctional Facility (4 of 5) (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 18)
  - Strike of 1979, Affidavits--Woodbourne Correctional Facility (5 of 5) (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 19)
  - Strike of 1979, Fact Sheets--Woodbourne Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 20)
  - Strike of 1979, Hearing Schedule--Woodbourne Correctional Facility, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 21)
  - Agreement of Reconciliation-Council 82 and New York State, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 22)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 23)
  - New York State v. AFSCME, Council 82, Order to Show Cause, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 24)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. New York State, Hugh Carey, Governor, Common Exhibits and Stipulations, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 25)
  - AFSCME, Council 82 v. New York State, Hugh Carey, Governor, Injunction Relief and Stipulations, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Legal Files), Folder 26)
- T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Officers) Files, 1983-1987; 4; 1.0 cubic ft.
  Contains T.U.F.C.O. charges and counter charges (1984), authorization card incidents (1984), and organizational activities (1985). T.U.F.C.O. challenged Council 82 as the exclusive bargaining representative for security and law enforcement personnel. Council 82 launched a counterattack on T.U.F.C.O. by developing anti-T.U.F.C.O. literature, a contest entitled, "Why I don't like T.U.F.C.0." and complaints filed against T.U.F.C.O. for using a logo similar to that of Council 82. Additional anti-T.U.F.C.O. materials Include sketches, cartoons, and the T.U.F.C.O. Constitution.
  - Affidavits, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 1)
  - Authorization Card Incidents, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 2)
  - Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 3)
  - Challenge to Council 82, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 4)
  - Challenge to Council 82 (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 5)
  - Challenge to Council 82 (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 6)
  - Charges (1 of 3 folders), 1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 7)
  - Charges (2 of 3 folders), 1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 8)
  - Charges (3 of 3 folders), 1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 9)
  - Charges and Counter Charges, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 11)
  - Council 82 Charges, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 12)
  - Distribution of Literature, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 13)
  - Improper Labor Practice, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 14)
  - Judicial Pabel Cases, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 15)
  - News Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 16)
  - Organizational Activities, 1983 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 17)
  - Organizational Activities, 1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 18)
  - T.U.F.C.O. Projects (AFSCME), 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 19)
  - Propaganda, 1987 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 20)
  - Representation Campaign Activities, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 21)
  - Representation Election, 1985 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 22)
  - Signers of T.U.F.C.O. Designation Card, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 23)
  - State of New York and T.U.F.C.O. Affidavits (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 24)
  - State of New York and T.U.F.C.O. Affidavits (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 25)
  - Why I Don't Like T.U.F.C.O. Contest, 1984 (Box 1 (4-T.U.F.C.O. (The Union of Federated Corrections Off), Folder 26)
- Sing Sing Local 1413, 1972-1980; 5; 0.25 cubic ft.
  Contains arbitration decisions (1979), constitution (1980), correspondence from the Department of Correctional Services (1972-79), and labor-management meetings (1978). The files of Sing Sing Local 1413 are a dozen or more folders pertaining exclusively to the local. Included within the series are correspondence with Council 82, arbitration decisions, and correspondence from the Minority Correction Officers Association. Local 1413 also publishes its own newsletter, "The Way Out," and maintained clippings and copies of printed articles on the New York State criminal justice system. This series is but a part of the records available for Sing Sing Local 1413. Additional records may be found throughout the Subject File series.
  - Arbitration, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 1)
  - Audit, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 2)
  - Constitution, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence From Dept. of Correctional Services, 1972-1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Council 82, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Ossining Correctional Facility, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 6)
  - Election, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meeting, 1973-1980 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 8)
  - Inmate Liaison Committee, Undated (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 9)
  - Labor-Management Meetings, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 10)
  - Memoranda From Local 1413 to Members, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 11)
  - Minority Corrections Officer's Association, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 12)
  - Newsletter--"The Way Out", Undated (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 14)
  - Strike of 1979 (Box 1 (5-Sing Sing Local 1413), Folder 15)
- Council 82 Newspapers, 1971-1989; 6; 1 reel of microfilm (Reel 1)
  Arranged chronologically by publication.
  Includes the Council 82 Review (1971, 1974, 1980-84) and the Council 82 Enforcer (1984-89). These publications serve the union by keeping the members abreast of the political as well as the social and economic climate of the New York State Department of Corrections. There are substantial gaps for the early years of the Council 82 Review with volumes 1-10 and 13-16 missing.
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 11, no. 7, 1971 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 11, no. 14, 1973 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 12, no. 25, 1974 February-1974 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 12, no. 27, 1974 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 12, no. 28, 1974 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 12, no. 29, 1974 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 12, no.31, 1974 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 17, no. 1, 1980 March-1980 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 17, no. 2, 1980 May-1980 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 17, no. 3, 1980 July-1980 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 17, no. 4, 1980 September-1980 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 17, no. 5, 1980 November-1980 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 1, 1981 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 2, 1981 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 3, 1981 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 4, 1981 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 5, 1981 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 6, 1981 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, no. 8, 1981 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, nos. 9 & 10, 1981 September-1981 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 18, nos. 11 & 12, 1981 November-1981 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, nos. 1 & 2, 1982 January-1982 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 3, 1982 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 4, 1982 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 5, 1982 May-1982 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 7, 1982 August-1982 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 8, 1982 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 9, 1982 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 19, no. 10, 1982 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 1, 1983 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 2, 1983 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 3, 1983 April 19 (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 4, 1983 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 5, 1983 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 6, 1983 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 7, 1983 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 8, 1983 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 9, 1983 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 10, 1983 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 11, 1983 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 20, no. 12, 1983 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 21, no. 1, 1984 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 21, no. 2, 1984 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 21, no. 3, 1984 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 21, no. 4, 1984 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Review, Vol. 21, no. 5, 1984 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 6, 1984 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 7, 1984 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 8, 1984 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 9, 1984 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 10, 1984 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 11, 1984 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 12, 1984 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 21, no. 13, 1984 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 1, 1985 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 2, 1985 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 3, 1985 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 4, 1985 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 5, 1985 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 6, 1985 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 7, 1985 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 8, 1985 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 9, 1985 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 10, 1985 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 11, 1985 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 22, no. 12, 1985 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 1, 1986 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 2, 1986 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 3, 1986 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 4, 1986 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 5, 1986 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 6, 1986 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 7, 1986 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 8, 1986 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 9, 1986 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 10, 1986 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 11, 1986 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 23, no. 12, 1986 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 1, 1987 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 2, 1987 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 3, 1987 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 4, 1987 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 5, 1987 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 6, 1987 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 7, 1987 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 8, 1987 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 9, 1987 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 10, 1987 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 11, 1987 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 24, no. 12, 1987 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 1, 1988 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 2, 1988 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 3, 1988 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 4, 1988 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 5, 1988 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 6, 1988 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 7, 1988 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 8, 1988 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 9, 1988 September (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 10, 1988 October (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 11, 1988 November (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 25, no. 12, 1988 December (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 1, 1989 January (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 2, 1989 February (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 3, 1989 March (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 4, 1989 April (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 5, 1989 May (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 6, 1989 June (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 7, 1989 July (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 8, 1989 August (Reel 1)
  - The Council 82 Enforcer, Vol. 26, no. 9, 1989 September (Reel 1)